A Guide to the Blake W. Corson, Jr., Papers, 1861-1984 (Bulk, 1934-1979)
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series V: Publications, Journals, and Reports, 1934-1982
  - Subseries C: Papers
    - "Net Energy Analysis of Ethanol Production," 1976 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - "New Aspects of Sound Generation by Circular Jets," 1972 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - "Oxygen: New Chemical for Pulp Industry," 1972, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - "Oxygen Seperated from Air Using Molecular Sieve," 1972 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - "A Preliminary Assment of the Feasibilty of Deriving Liquid and Gaseous Fuels from Grown and Waste Organics," 1976 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - "Propulsive Efficiency of Tail Mounted Turbofan Engines," 1968 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - "Simple Pressure Source Model of Jet Noise," Ca. 1971,1972 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - "Simplified Propeller Calculations," 1938 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - "The Solution of Isentropic Transonic Flow," 1972 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - "Some Details of the Structure of an Axis Symetric" (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - "Some Experiments on Two Stream Propelling Nozzles for Supersonic Aircraft," 1970 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - "Supersonic Annular Nozzles," 1971 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - "Tables for Compressible Flow for a Gamma of 1.266," 1967 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - "On the Thermodynamic Spectrum of Air Breating Propulsion," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - "The Theory of Ejectors," 1945 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - "Vortex Decay about a Stationary Boundary," 1967 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Subseries D: Journals
    - Sub-subseries i: Journal of Aeronautical Sciences
      - Journal of Aeronautical Scienes: Volume 8, Number 9, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Journal of Aeronautical Scienes: Volume 11, Number 5, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Journal of Aeronautical Scienes: Volume 16, Number 5, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Journal of Aeronautical Scienes: Volume 16, Number 2, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Sub-subseries ii: Journal of Energy
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 1, Number 1, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 1, Number 2, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 1, Number 3, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 1, Number 4, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 1, Number 5, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 1, Number 6, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 2, Number 1, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 2, Number 2, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 2, Number 3, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 2, Number 4, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 2, Number 5, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 2, Number 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 3, Number 1, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 3, Number 2, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 3, Number 3, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 3, Number 4, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 3, Number 5, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 3, Number 6, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 4, Number 1, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 4, Number 2, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 4, Number 3, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 4, Number 4, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 4, Number 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 4, Number 6, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 5, Number 1, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Journal of Energy: Volume 5, Number 2, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - The Virginia Engineer: Volume 27, Number 8, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Subseries E: Articles
    - Annual Reiew of Energy, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - "Anit-Icing Cuts [nu]sub-prop Less Than Moderate Icing," 1949 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - "Aircraft propulsions Systems in Evolution," 1965 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - "Astronaut Defends U.S. Space Program During Dedication," 1970 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - "Charge Analyzer for Aerosols and Sprays," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - "Comparisons of Free Flight and Wind Tunnel Data on Slender Cones," 1965 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - "The Compressible Discharge Coefficient of a Borda-Pipe and Other Nozzles," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - "Compressible Flow Through a Two Dimensional Slit, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - "Conductivity of Dust Laden Gases," 1965 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - "Discharge Coefficient Characteristics of Orfices," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - "Dynamics of Bilaterally Symetric Vortex Rings," 1971 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - "The Effects of Exhaust Nozzle Recombination on Hypersonic Ramjet Performance," 1963 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - "The Effect of Jet Entrainment on Lift and Moment for a Thin Aerofoil with Blowing," 1963, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - "An Equation for the Entrainment of Ejectors" (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - "Flow Field in A Swirl Chamber," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - "Fuel and Feedstock from Refuse," 1976 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - "Handbook of Solid Waste Disposal Materials and Energy Recovery," Ca. 1976 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - "History of the NACA," 1965, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - "How to Prevent and Remove Mildew," 1976 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - "How Much Defense?," 1968 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - "Hypersonic Propulsion," 1965 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - "Hysteresis in the Flow Through an Orfice," 1966 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - "Influence of a Jet on the Aerodynamic Properties of Wings Positioned Above the Jet," 1970 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - "LRC Turboprop Research to Support LeRC Propulsion/Airframs Integration," 1976, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - "The Maximum Attainable Pressure in a Moving Gas-Vacuum- Atmosphere System," n.d. (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - "The Motion of a Two Dimensionsl Bouyant Vortex," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - "Nozzle Discharge Coefficient," 1970 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - "Pressure Change Accompanying Mixing Two Ideal Gases," 1971 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - "Processing Energy from Wastes," Ca. 1976 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - "Propelling Nozzle Research," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - "James J. Kilpatrick: Questions Things They Ought Not to Have Done," 1972 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - "The Stability of Viscous Fluid Between Cylinders with an Axial Flow," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - "Sink Vorticies and Whirlwinds," 1964 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - "Scientists Tackle Jet Noise Problem," 1956 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - "SpaceCraft Radiators," 1962 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - "Some Experiments on an Engine Installed Above the Wing," 1970 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - "Soviet Physics Acoustics," 1965 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - "Suggests Look at Disposal Systems," 1965 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - "The Turborocket for High Speed Air Breathing Vehicles," 1965 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - "A Windstorm That Blows Good!" 1971 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Subseries F: Pamplets, Brochures, and Directories
    - Air Scoop Langley Newsletter, 1947-1960 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Aviation Week and Space Technology XC-142A Pamphlet, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Contact Lenses Coupon, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Directory for Langley Research Center, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Directory for Langley Research Center, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Directory for Langley Research Center, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Langley Research Center: Personnel Newsletter (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - McDonnell Douglas--Brochure/Map, 1967, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - NACA Fortieth Anniversary, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - "NACA-LMAL and You" (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - NACA Reunion: Ashville, North Carolina, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - NASA Fiftieth Aniversiary Celebration, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - "Nuclear Attack and Industrial Survival," 1962 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Society of Automotive Engineers--Brochures/Pamphlets, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - S.A.E.: Aeronautical and Air Transport Meeting, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Tech Brief (Catergory 2): Prediction of Friction Coefficients for Gases, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - "A Visit to Langley Research Center," 1970 (Box 9, Folder 17)